Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence
    - Jones, Sabrina, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Jordan, Michael, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Jordan-Hayes, Nikki and Michael, undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Joy, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Joy and John, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Joyce K., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Juan G., 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Judy and David, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Judy, ca. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Julia, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Julie, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Julie, Undated (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Julie and Glenn, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - K., 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - K. B., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - K Brew, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - K., Constantine, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Kahane, Lisa, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Kahn, Robin, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Kamen, Steven, Genisia, Anna and Emily, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Kane, Louisa / Management Consultants for the Arts, Inc., 1992 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Kaneshiro, Cheryl; Toporowicz, Maciek, Undated (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Kanter, Norbert, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Kapadia, Heena; Morris, Ted, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Kaplan, Daile, 1978-2001; Undated (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Kaplan, Janet, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Kaplan, Karen / The Rockefeller Foundation, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Kaplan, Steven, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Kaps, Amy, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Karalis, Constantine, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Karen, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Karen, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Karin and Jonathan, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Karla, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Karoly, Tardos, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Kasper, 1998; Undated (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Katchen, Michael; Varni, Suzanne, 1987-2007 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Kate, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Kathy, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Katie, Don, and Nathaniel, 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Katzowitz, Lauren, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Kaufmann / Joroff, 1992-2004; Undated (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Kawamata. Tadashi, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Kaz, Donna, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Keepers of the Waters, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Keith, Jon, Undated (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Kendall, Sherwood M., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Kennedy, Katy, 2001; Undated (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - Kennedy, Meaghan, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - Kenneth, 1976-1979; Undated (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Kenny, Kay / Heresies, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Kern, William Bliem, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Kerrin, Jessica, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Kershbaumer, Sharon, 1979-1988 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Khanna, Shama, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - Killacky, John, Undated (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - Kim, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Kim, Undated (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Kimbro, Ernestine, 1993-2007 (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Kindred, Audrey, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - King Tut [Crawford, Pepper], 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - Kings County Clerk, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - Kinsman, Eric, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 146)
    - Kipperman, Deanna/Marvin Shoes, undated (Box 13, Folder 147)
    - Kitchel, Nancy, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - Klayman, Melinda, 1990-1998, undated (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Klein, Mary, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Klick, Laurel, 1977-1992 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Kno, Nina and Lorin Rosen, 2005, undated (Box 13, Folder 152)
    - Knox, Sonia, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Koh, Germaine/National Gallery of Canada, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Komar and Melmid, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Komlosi, Alexander, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 156)
    - Komnenic, Dusanka, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Korn, Henry, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 158)
    - Kos, Joe, 159 (Box 13, Folder 159)
    - Kouns, Marjorie, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    - [Kovanuk] family, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 161)
    - Kozloff, Joyce, 1985-2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 162)
    - Krall, Lisa and Edward Bahlman, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 163)
    - Krarup, Helge, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 164)
    - Krais, Lea, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 165)
    - Kreiling, Amy, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 166)
    - Kresler, Lillian, 1984-1989 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Krigbaum, Megan, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Krims, Les, undated (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Kris, undated (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Krolack, Karn, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Krochmal, Walter, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Kroezen, Jill, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Krulick, Barbara and Eileen Guggenheim/ New York Academy of Art, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Kuffler, Suzanne, 1985-2006, undated (Box 13, Folder 176)
    - Kulick, Sharon, 1972-2005, undated (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Kulterman, Udo, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Kunin, Julia, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Kurnos, Jill, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Kurtis, Luke, 2000; contains CD (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - L, undated (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - L. E., 1984 (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - L.M., 1984 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - L. Barbara, undated (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - LaBerteaux, Hannah, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Labowitz, Leslie and Suzanne Lacy, undated (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Lacey, Suzanne, 1976-2008, undated (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - Lady Pink, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - Lahr, Christin, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 190)
    - Lamarre, Paul and Melissa Wolf, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Lance, Dean/ Video Data Bank, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lance, Dean, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lane, Barbara, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lang, Avis, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Lanyon, Ellen, 1989-1996, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Lanz, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Lanzillotto, Annie, 1997-2003, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The Lapp Princess, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Laren, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Larry, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Larsen, Sandee, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - LaTourette, Harvey, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - [Laura], undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Lauren, 1980, illegible (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Lauren/ Ms. Magazine, 1996, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Lauridsen, Hanne, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Lawton, Linda, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Loue, Marjorie, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Lawrence, Matthew, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Lawrence, Paula Fried, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Lawrence, Paula S., 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Lawrie, Karen, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Lazer Park, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Lea, 1988, illegible (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Leah, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Leatherdale, Marcus, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Leda, Ann, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Lederman, Stephanie Brody, 1986-2007 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Lee and Barbara, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Lees, Ming Wei, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Leeser, Peter/Northwest Natural, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Leeser, Thomas and Alison Saar, 1989-1997 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Leeser, Tom and Cal Arts Integrated Media, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Leeson, Lynn Hershmann, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Lefever, Odie, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Leff, Gabby, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Left, Sarah, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Leftoverz, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Lehmann, Carola, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Lehmann, Minnette, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Lehrer, Jennifer, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Lehrer, Phyllis and Richard, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Leila, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Leo, Vince, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Lencek, Bibi, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Lens, Bob, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Lerner, Adam/The Lab, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Leroy, A., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Lescher, Nita, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Leslie, David, 1987-2005 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Leslie, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Letters to the Editor, The New York Times, 1995-2004 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Levine, Les, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Levine, Roberta, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Levine, Sam, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Lewenz, Lisa, 1983-2007 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Lewis, Jessie Jane, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Li, Hanquan/China Workers' Center for International Exchange, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Libow, Sue, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Lichty, Stephen, 2006, undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Lieberman, Claire, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Linden, Amy, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Linn, Nancy/Printed Matter, 1987, undated (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Lipnack, Jessica, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Lippard, Lucy, 1972-2005 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Lisa, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Lisa, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Liss, Fred, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Lissa, 1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - List, Larry, 2002 and date illegible (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Lister, Ardele, 1978-2003 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Livingston, Dr. and Mre. P.O., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Livingston-Broome, Helen, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Liz, 1984, undated (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Lloyd, Gary, undated (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Lock and Ally, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Locke, Charmaine, Splendora/Huston and James Sarls, undated (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Logemann, Jand and Gerry Rosen, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Logue, Alexandra/Baruch College, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Lolo, Lulu, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Long, Mary Ellen, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Carey Lovelace, 1996-2003 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Lovelinks, Valentine, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Lovett, Ann, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Lovett, Laura, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council/Greta Gunderson, 2002-2005 (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Lubousky, Susan, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Lucy, 1978-1984, date illegible (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - Lucy and Becky, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Ludwig, Tiffany, 2000-2006 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Lyle, Joanne, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Lynn, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Lynch, Ron/ The Institute for Art and Urban Resources, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Lyon, Jessa, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Lyons, Joan, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - M, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - M, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - M, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - M, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - M, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - M, undated (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - M/ Heathcote Art Foundation, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - M + W, date illegible (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - M. B., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - M. [ Hashs], date illegible (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - Mabe, Joni, 1986-2003 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Mac, Taylor, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - McAllister, Pam/Barbara Deming Memorial Fund, undated (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - MacArthur Fellows Program/Daniel Socalow, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - McCarney, Scott, 1998-2006, undated (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - McCauley, Robbie, 2000, untitled (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - McClurg, John, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - McCray, Kelly and Annette Larson/ Mercer Union, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - McDonough, Melissa/ School of the Art Institute of Chicago, undated (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - McGill, Dominic, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - McGinnis, Mark, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - McGough, Laura, 1999-2007 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - McGrath, Diane, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - McKeon, Tom, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - McKenna, Rebecca, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - McKereghan, Dan, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - McLaughlin, Jean, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - McLaughlin, Thom/USF, 1997, undated (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - MacLennan, Alistair, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - MacLennan, Toby, illegible (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - McMahon, Paul, 1973-1997, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - McNeil/Tucker, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Macrobiotic Association of Connecticut, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - Magee, Jennifer and Champe Smith, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - Maghocco, Lavinia and Stanley Mass, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Mah, Angela/Daina, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Maine College of Art/Christine Vincent, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Mainwaring, Martha, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Mailwald, Carl, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Maiwald, Christa and Mark Segal, 2000-2006 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Malatesta, John, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Malcolm, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Malen, Lenore, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Malenky, Eda and Alan Rosner, undated (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Malloy, Judy, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - Malpede, John, 1979-1987 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Mandel, Carol/New York University, 2003-2007 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Mandel, Mike, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Manhattan Neighborhood Network, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Manhattan Youth Recreation, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Manos, Kenna, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Mantara, undated (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust, 1985, undated (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Maran, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Maran, Maeve and Wayne Pambianchi, 1980-2002 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Maran, Maeve, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Marc, undated (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Margaret, undated (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - [Margaret], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Marge and Sandy, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 151)
    - Marian, undated (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Marian, 1972, undated (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Mark, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Markisch, Sven, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Marim, undated (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Martha, undated (Box 14, Folder 157)
    - Martin, Pedro, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    - Martinazzoli, Luca, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    - Martinez, Daniel Joseph, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Marty, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - Marty and Glenn, undated (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Marty and Randy, undated (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Mary, 1989-1995, undated (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Mary, undated (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Mary and Tom, undated (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Mary Theresa, undated (Box 14, Folder 167)
    - Matherson, Nichelle/College Art Association, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 168)
    - Matta, Susan, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Mattern, Yvette, undated (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - Maureen, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Mavor, Anne, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - [Maubel], Carol, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Maya, 1989-2003, undated (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Mayer, Rosemary, undated (Box 14, Folder 175)
    - Meier, Yvonne, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Melchert, Mary Ann and Jim, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Melinda, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Melby, Julia/ Toledo Museum of Art, 2000-2001, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Mendoza, Dorotea, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mercer Union/Anette Larson, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Merchant, Shabnam, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mercy, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Meris, Doneley/HIV Arts Network, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Mermelstein, Jeff, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Messinger, Ruth, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Messner, Ann, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Mew. Tommy, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Meyer, Deborah, 1987-2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Meyers, Michael, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Michael, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Michael, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Michael, 1979-1985, date illegible (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Michael, 1972-1982, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence from Wilson to Michael, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mike, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Mike, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Miller, Jen, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Miller, Jennifer, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Miller, Larry V., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Miller-Keller, Andrea and Tony Keller, 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Mills, Chris, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Mills, Lynn, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Milman, Estera, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Minarelli, Enzo, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Mira, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Mitchell, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Mobley, Vanessa, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Mockman, Paul, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Mogul, Susan, 1981-2007, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Mohammed, Centro di Comunicazione Ristretta, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Montgomery, Ken, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Moore, Alan, 2007, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Moore, Frank, 1995-2001, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Moore, George, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Moore, John, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Moore, Townie, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Monchik, Lauren/ Ms. Magazine, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Monsod, Trinket, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Montano, Linda, 1981-2000, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Montclair State College/ Caron Van Gilder, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Morello, Terry, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Moren, Lisa, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Morgan, Carol, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Morin, France/ 49th Parallel, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Morrell, Pearl, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Morris, Catherine, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Morris, Nancie, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Morris, Penny and Julie, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Morris, Penny and Robert, 1977-2008, undated (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Morris, W.E., date illegible (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Morris-Martel, Gay and Emily, 1986-1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Mosakowski, Susan, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Moss, Lawrence, 1995-2006 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Moss, Stanley, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Motson, Don, 1976-1986 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Mouraud, Tania, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Moya and Pink, undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Moya, S and E, undated (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1995 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Muel, Susanne, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Mueller, Susanne, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Muller, Elizabeth, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Multiple names, 1982-2005, undated (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Multiple, Birthday Party, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - The Municipal Art Society/ Gloria Troy, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Munn, Norma P., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Munrre, Alexandra, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Murphy, Charlotte/ National Association of Artist's Organizations, 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Murphy, Pat, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Murphy, Suzanne, undated (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Murray, Ian, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Murrin, Tom, 1983-2002, undated (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Murthy, Sheelah, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - The Muse Museum, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Myerson, Bess, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - N, Jack and Alice, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Naidus, Beverly and Bob Spivey, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Nakka, Deborah, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Nancy, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Nao, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Nathan, undated (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Nathan and Genie, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - National Assembly on Arts, Organizing and Environmental Justice, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - National Association of Artists' Organizations, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - National Campaign for Freedom of Expression, 1992-1995 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - National Coalition Against Censorship/Joan Borfin, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - National Cultural Alliance/ Able, Edward, Kathy Dwyer Southern, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - National Endowmnet for the Arts, 1981-1987 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - National Gallery of Canada, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - National Studio Program, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - National Visual Arts Guild/ Daniel Tisdale, 1998-2001 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - Naylor, Penelope, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - Neary, Scott, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Necol, Jane, 1997-2004 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - [Nees], Susan, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Nemec, Vernita, 1985-1995 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Nesbett, Peter, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Neshat, Shirin, 1991-1993, undated (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - Neu, Jim, 1986-1995 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - The New Cinema, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - New Jersey City University, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - New Museum/ Sarah Farsad, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - New Observations/ Erika Knerr, 1993, undated (Box 15, Folder 109)
    - New School for Social Research, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 110)
    - New York City Arts Coalition, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    - New York City Transit Authority, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1985-2008 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - New York Institute for the Humanities/ Aileen Ward, 1992-1995, undated (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - New York University, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - New York University/ Faculty Resource Network, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - New York University/ Gallatin Arts and Society Committee, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Newman, Amy, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Newman, Michael, 1988-1991, date illegible (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Newmark, Susan, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Nichio, Linda, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Nina, undated (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Nix, Marilyn, 1977-1994 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Noble, Sabine and Anja Mayer, undated (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Nolan, Janet, 1988-2004, undated (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Nolan, Patti, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - North Miami Center of Contemporary Art/ Lou Anne Colodny, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Not in Our Name, undated (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Novak, Barbara and Brian O'Doherty, 1984-1989 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - Novak, Linda, 1983-1992 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Novelli, Patricia, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - Novey, Judith, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - O., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - O'brien, Mern/ Dalhousie University, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - Obrien, Mark/ Davis, Polk and Wardwell, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - O'Doherty, Barbara and Brian, 1990-2008 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - O'Donghue/Caddy, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - O'Donoghue, Carrie, 2004-2007 (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - Oerlemans, Marguerite, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - O'Farrell, Dierdre, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - O'Grady, Lorraine, 1989-2008 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    - Oji, Helen, 1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - Oleszko, Pat, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - Olin, Ferris, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - Ontario Arts Council, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - Ontario College of Art and Design/ J. Anthony Caldwell, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - Ortiz, Raphael, 1988-1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - Osei-Boateng, Lillian, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - O'Sullivan, Annie, 1983-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ott, James, 1967-1968, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ottergibbon, Kelly, Cole and Tom, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Owen, Taylor, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - P., Adam, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - PS 122/ Dominick Balletta/ Anne Dennin, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Pace, Linda/Art Pace (Box 16, Folder 7)